Wendy Natalia Peña Acosta

International Business / Marketing

Double bachelor's degree at Santo Tomás Unibersity. International Business (Graduated) and marketing (Senior year). Bilingual (English-Spanish), with communicative and negotiation skills. High degree of commitment, creativity and leadership. Experience in the management of CRM and market intelligence at the international level.



Personal Info

Address

Calle 135 B # 108 -09

Bogotá, Colombia

Phone

+(57) 3014238244

E-mail

natalia.acosta122@gmail.com

Place of birth

Bogotá

Date of birth

1994-11-11

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/natalia-peña-acosta



Languages

English B2

Advanced English. Wall Street Institute. Bogotá, 2017.

Spanish





Skills

Digital Marketing

Google

Adwords



Office

Euromonitor

Google

AdWords

Photoshop • • • • • •



Experience

2016-07 - International Business Intern

2017-01 CasaLuker SA

- Optimization of the international commercial information management to the elaboration, control and monitoring of KPIs needed for the demand handling and fulfillment of commercial objectives.
- Design and execution of the international CRM plan: selection and validation of information, identification of potential clients (50 clients), and integration into the web platform.
- Successful performance in international clients meetings that allowed to improve the commercial relations and strengthen the image of the mark.



Additional Activities - Entrepreneurship

2015-08 -

2016-04

CEO

Industrias Textiles S.A.S

- Design and development of the business plan Legalization of the company.
- Planning and successful participation in events such as brand launch and business fairs. Third place at the "Tomasino entrepreneurship fair", more than 50 participating companies.
- Duplication of working capital in the first month of operation.
- Design and execution of the social media strategy.



Education

2012-01 - International Business, Santo Tomás University

2017-03 Honorary Diploma Cum Laude, Academic excellence

2014-08 - Marketing, Santo Tomás University



present

Courses

2016	7th International Congress RACNI (Academic Network of Commerce and
	International Business), Santo Tomás University
2016	IV International Marketing Seminar, Santo Tomás University
2017-09	Marketing digital, Marketing Digital Academy, Bogotá
2017 -	Digital marketing, "Actívate Google", IAB Spain (Interactive Advertising
present	Bureau)